Yes, brother, Samsung people say that
our Galaxy S24 Ultra
is the mobile with the best camera in the world and Google
people also say that Pixel 8 Pro
is the mobile with the best camera and even
Apple people say that iPhone 15
Pro Max is the mobile with the best camera in the world.
But brother, all these things are
absolutely wrong.  Hey brother, don't do this here, I am
telling you the truth.  This mobile is
not the mobile with the best camera in the world but it is something
else.  How did you know?  Brother,
I know everything.  So brother, this is the
mobile with the best camera in the world which is the
father of all these mobiles.  This mobile has a
three camera setup in the rear.  50-
megapixel main camera, 180-megapixel
tertiscope telephoto camera.